gunsinternational.com 2019-07-14

# Privacy Statement

Effective Date: November 1, 2006

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Personally identifiable information you provide GunsInternational.com, when you register will not be sold or given to outside sources without your permission. Third-party providers featured on or linked to by our website, such as vendors of products and services offered through our site by third parties, may be gathering information, as well, through processes we don't control.

**Searches and Listings**

To make use of certain features on our site, visitors need to provide limited information about themselves and their interests so that we can tailor the information we provide to their needs. For example, to help you find an item you want close to home, we need to know what kind of item you're looking for and your zip code. We ask you to provide this information when you perform a search. We use this information to help you find the gun you're looking for. If you find a listing that interests you and elect to send the seller an email through our website, we'll share with the seller the contact information you supply through our online "Contact Seller" form. If you do not wish to share your email address or other contact information with the sellers who advertise on our website, you should not use our "Contact Seller" contact form. Many of the seller listings that appear on our website include telephone numbers that can be used to contact the seller that is selling the advertised item. When you list an item for sale, we ask for information on the item and on how you can be contacted by potential buyers. We also ask for your credit card number and the expiration date on your card. We use this information to create your ad and to process your payment.

**Email Addresses**

If you provide us your email address, we may email you about our website or our services, or to inquire about your experience using our website or sites operated by others. From time to time, we'll also send you emails that may include gun information, special promotions and other commercial offers that we think may be of interest to you. Though we hope you'll find these communications informative and useful, if you don't, you can always unsubscribe by following the simple instructions included in each email.

**Cookies**

To help us tailor our website to the needs and interests of our visitors, we keep track of the pages visited by our users by placing a cookie, a small entry in text file, on your hard drive. The cookie contains an ID number that allows us to track the pages you've visited. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our site by making it more responsive to the needs of our users. Cookies don't reveal personal information; the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Cookies can't read unrelated data off your hard drive. Our advertisers and those who provide products and/or services through our site may also assign their own cookies, a process we don't control. We don't have access to these cookies or to any information they contain. The help function on most web browsers contains information on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie or to disable cookies entirely. However, if you don't accept cookies, you won't be able to take advantage of various features on our site that are available to other visitors.

**Web Beacons**

To help us keep track of how many users are visiting particular pages within our website, and how many users are accessing particular listings that we distribute, we may place a small file, called a web beacon, on some of our pages and on some of the listings we distribute. These web beacons allow us to track the number of users that view our pages and our listings, but they don't reveal any personally identifying information about individual users.

**Browser Level Information**

Our web server automatically collects limited information about your computer configuration when you visit our site, including the type of browser software you use, the operating system you're running, the resolution of your computer monitor, the website that referred you, and your IP address. (Your IP address is a numerical address that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you want to view) can be transmitted to you. We also use IP address information for systems administration and trouble shooting purposes. Your IP address does not tell us who you are.) We use this information to make our site as useful as we can for as many users as possible.

**USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

When we present information to our advertisers-to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website--it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site. Any credit card information you may provide to us is secured during transmission over the Internet using industry--standard secure socket layer (SSL) encryption and is stored on our secure servers. (See "Security," below.) We use your credit card information only to bill you for the services you order from us. We don't share your credit card information with anyone, except as may be necessary to process your transactions or comply with law. We may collect, or have a third party collect on our behalf, aggregated statistical information about how visitors use and navigate around our site, such as the number of users who visit various pages within the site, what they click on, whether they scroll up or down on particular pages, fill out forms, etc. This aggregated information does not identify you personally. We use this information to improve our site. We may also disclose this aggregated information to third parties.

**WHO WILL HAVE ACCESS TO MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Our priority is to keep your personal information private and confidential. GunsInternational.com will not willfully disclose, rent, or sell your personal information to third parties. However, certain personal information will be available to others in the process of using GunsInternational.com. For example, visitors to GunsInternational.com may view your member name, items you have for sale and other profile information you release in your ads.

Of course, once you provide personal information to a buyer or seller, GunsInternational.com has no control over how that information might be used by that individual. Given the abuses available via the internet, we recommend using our messaging system for any communications between you and potential buyers and sellers.

GunsInternational.com may choose to disclose your personally identifiable information to others under the following circumstances: you consent to share your information: in response to a criminal investigation, subpoena, court order or legal process:your actions on GunsInternational.com appear to be in violation of our policies (including, but not limited to, our Classified Ad Guidelines, User Agreement, and Fees and Payments policies): you post a classified ad which we believe, in our sole discretion, may create a liability for GunsInternational.com.

**LINKS AND FEATURES OFFERED IN CONJUNCTION WITH OTHER PROVIDERS**

To make our website more valuable to our visitors, our site includes links to other websites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don't control. The provider's privacy policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of our provider partners via a link either from their site's homepage or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information.

**SECURITY**

Information we gather on our website is stored within GunsInternational.com-controlled databases (or databases hosted on our behalf) on servers maintained in protected environments. Any credit card information you provide us is secured for transmission over the Internet using industry-standard secure sockets layer (SSL) encryption. However, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our servers or databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a vehicle listing is available to anyone with Internet access.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

The Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we'll post the changes to this Privacy Statement on this website and update the reference to the effective date to reflect the date of the amendment. By visiting GunsInternational.com, you agree that your visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Statement and our User Agreement. Nothing in this policy shall limit, prohibit, or otherwise deny the ability of GunsInternational.com to (1) transfer, assign, or sell our assets to a third party without limitation, or (2) dispose of our assets in any manner. In addition, GunsInternational.com makes no warranties or claims regarding the accuracy or completeness of the information we collect and disclose through our site, and disclaims any liability regarding its use.

**RELEASE AND INDEMNIFICATION**

BY USING OUR WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO THE FOLLOWING:

TO INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS GUNS INTERNATIONAL, ITS OWNERS, EMPLOYEES AND REPRESENTATIVES AND LICENSEES FROM, AGAINST AND IN RESPECT OF ALL ACTIONS, SUITS, PROCEEDINGS, DEMANDS, JUDGMENTS, COSTS AND EXPENSES INCIDENT TO, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, GUNSINTERNATIONAL.COM, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO YOUR USE OF THE GUNSINTERNATIONAL.COM WEBSITE, ANY LISTING YOU PLACE THROUGH THE GUNSINTERNATIONAL.COM WEBSITE AND/OR ANY OF THE SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH THE GUNSINTERNATIONAL.COM WEBSITE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE FOREGOING FOR BODILY INJURY, DEATH OR DISABILITY.

TO REMISE, RELEASE, AQUIT, SATISFY, AND FOREVER DISCHARGE GUNSINTERNATIONAL.COM, OF AND FROM ALL, AND ALL MANNER OF ACTION AND ACTIONS, CAUSE AND CAUSES OF ACTIONS, SUITS, DEBTS, DUES, SUMS OF MONEY, ACCOUNTS, RECKONINGS, BONDS, BILLS, SPECIALTIES, COVENANTS, CONTRACTS, CONTROVERSIES, AGREEMENTS, PROMISES, VARIANCES, TRESPASSES, DAMAGES, JUDGMENTS, EXECUTIONS, CLAIMS AND DEMANDS WHATSOEVER, IN LAW OR EQUITY, WHICH YOU EVER HAD, NOW HAVE, OR WHICH ANY REPRESENTATIVE, SUCCESSOR, OR ASSIGN OF YOU, HEREAFTER CAN, SHALL OR MAY HAVE, AGAINST GUNSINTERNATIONAL.COM, FOR, UPON OR BY REASON OF ANY MATTER, CAUSE OR THING WHATSOEVER, FROM THE BEGINNING OF THE WORLD TO THE DAY OF THESE PRESENTS.
